Archives Union File on Microfilm 6046 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Archives Union File on Microfilm
0000-2999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
6046 mf
56.25 cubic feet
486 microfilm reels
Articles, reprints, pamphlets, publications, microfilm.
8036805
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 30, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 30, 2014
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
8036805
- ACA News (Reel 1) (Reel 1)
- Annual Meat Cutters and Butchers (Reel 1) (Reel 2)
- Annual Meat Cutters and Butchers (Reel 2) (Reel 3)
- Annual Meat Cutters and Butchers (Reel 3) (Reel 4)
- The American Socialist (Reel 1) (Reel 5)
- Arbeidenen (Reel 1) (Reel 6)
- Asbestos Worker (Reel 1) (Reel 7)
- Asbestos Worker (Reel 2) (Reel 8)
- Beaver Factory Labor History Journal (Reel 1) (Reel 9)
- Binghamton Advocate (Reel 1) (Reel 10)
- Brick Myers and Mason (Reel 1) (Reel 11)
- Black Worker (Reel 1) (Reel 12)
- Black Worker (Reel 2) (Reel 13)
- Black Worker (Reel 3) (Reel 14)
- Boilermakers Blacksmiths Journal (Reel 1) (Reel 15)
- Boilermakers Blacksmiths Journal (Reel 2) (Reel 16)
- Boilermakers Blacksmiths Journal (Reel 3) (Reel 17)
- Boilermakers Blacksmiths Journal (Reel 4) (Reel 18)
- Boilermakers Blacksmiths Journal (Reel 5) (Reel 19)
- Boilermakers Blacksmiths Journal (Reel 6) (Reel 20)
- Boilermakers Blacksmiths Journal (Reel 7) (Reel 21)
- Boilermakers Blacksmiths Journal (Reel 8) (Reel 22)
- Boilermakers Blacksmiths Journal (Reel 9) (Reel 23)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers Journal (Reel 1) (Reel 24)
- The Brewery Worker (Reel 1) (Reel 25)
- Buffalo Socialist (Reel 1) (Reel 26)
- Bulletin (NYS Federation of Labor) (Reel 1) (Reel 27)
- Butte Anaconda Joint Strike Bulletin (Reel 1) (Reel 28)
- The CIO News (Reel 1) (Reel 29)
- CIO News (Reel 1) (Reel 30)
- CIO News (Reel 2) (Reel 31)
- CIO News (Reel 3) (Reel 32)
- Carpenter (Reel 1) (Reel 33)
- Cafeteria Call (Reel 1) (Reel 34)
- The Chief (Reel 1) (Reel 35)
- The Chief (Reel 2) (Reel 36)
- The Chief (Reel 3) (Reel 37)
- The Chief (Reel 4) (Reel 38)
- The Chief (Reel 5) (Reel 39)
- The Chief (Reel 6) (Reel 40)
- The Chief (Reel 7) (Reel 41)
- The Child Labor Bulletin (Reel 1) (Reel 42)
- The Child Labor Bulletin (Reel 2) (Reel 43)
- Cigar Makers (Reel 1) (Reel 44)
- Cigar Makers (Reel 2) (Reel 45)
- Cigar Makers (Reel 3) (Reel 46)
- Cigar Makers (Reel 4) (Reel 47)
- Cigar Makers (Reel 5) (Reel 48)
- Connecticut CIO Vanguard (Reel 1) (Reel 49)
- Connecticut CIO Vanguard (Reel 2) (Reel 50)
- Consolidator (Reel 1) (Reel 51)
- Daily People (Reel 1) (Reel 52)
- Daily People (Reel 2) (Reel 53)
- Daily People (Reel 3) (Reel 54)
- Daily People (Reel 4) (Reel 55)
- The Department Store Employee (Reel 1) (Reel 56)
- District 50 News (Reel 1) (Reel 57)
- Employer and Employed (Reel 1) (Reel 58)
- Electrical Worker (Reel 1) (Reel 59)
- Electrical Worker (Reel 2) (Reel 60)
- Electrical Worker (Reel 3) (Reel 61)
- Electrical Worker (Reel 4) (Reel 62)
- Cataloged NYSSILR (Reel 1) (Reel 63)
- Cataloged NYSSILR (Reel 2) (Reel 64)
- Farmer Labor Leader (Reel 1) (Reel 65)
- Federal Record (Reel 1) (Reel 66)
- Force Ouvier (Reel 1) (Reel 67)
- Force Ouvier (Reel 2) (Reel 68)
- Forts Hritt (Reel 1) (Reel 69)
- Freedom (Reel 1) (Reel 70)
- Freedom (Reel 2) (Reel 71)
- Frontpage (Reel 1) (Reel 72)
- The Fur Worker (Reel 1) (Reel 73)
- The Government Standard (Reel 1) (Reel 74)
- The Government Standard (Reel 2) (Reel 75)
- Great Lakes Sailor (Reel 1) (Reel 76)
- Great Lakes Sea Farer (Reel 1) (Reel 77)
- The Guide (Reel 1) (Reel 78)
- The Guild Reporter (Reel 1) (Reel 79)
- The Guild Reporter (Reel 2) (Reel 80)
- The Hat Reporter (Reel 1) (Reel 81)
- Cataloged IUE-CIO News (Reel 1) (Reel 82)
- Cataloged IUE-CIO News (Reel 2) (Reel 83)
- Industrial Worker (Reel 1) (Reel 84)
- Industrial Worker (Reel 2) (Reel 85)
- The Intercollegiate Socialist (Reel 1) (Reel 86)
- International Information (Reel 1) (Reel 87)
- International Musician (Reel 1) (Reel 88)
- International Musician (Reel 2) (Reel 89)
- International Woodworker (Reel 1) (Reel 90)
- Irish Worker (Reel 1) (Reel 91)
- Iron Molder's International Journal (Reel 1) (Reel 92)
- Journal of Switchmen's Union of N.A. (Reel 1) (Reel 93)
- Journal of Switchmen's Union of N.A. (Reel 2) (Reel 94)
- Journal of the Knights of Labor (Reel 1) (Reel 95)
- Journal of the Knights of Labor (Reel 2) (Reel 96)
- Journal of the Knights of Labor (Reel 3) (Reel 97)
- Journal of the Knights of Labor (Reel 4) (Reel 98)
- Journal of the Knights of Labor (Reel 5) (Reel 99)
- Journal of the Knights of Labor (Reel 6) (Reel 100)
- Justice (Reel 1) (Reel 101)
- Justice (Reel 2) (Reel 102)
- Justice (Reel 3) (Reel 103)
- Justice ILGWU (Reel 1) (Reel 104)
- Justice ILGWU (Reel 2) (Reel 105)
- Justice ILGWU (Reel 3) (Reel 106)
- Justice ILGWU (Reel 4) (Reel 107)
- Justice ILGWU (Reel 5) (Reel 108)
- Justice ILGWU (Reel 6) (Reel 109)
- Justice ILGWU (Reel 7) (Reel 110)
- Justice ILGWU (Reel 8) (Reel 111)
- Justice ILGWU (Reel 9) (Reel 112)
- Justice ILGWU (Reel 10) (Reel 113)
- Justice ILGWU (Reel 11) (Reel 114)
- Justice ILGWU (Reel 12) (Reel 115)
- Justice ILGWU (Reel 13) (Reel 116)
- Justice ILGWU (Reel 14) (Reel 117)
- The National Trades Union (Reel 1) (Reel 118)
- Cataloged (Reel 1) (Reel 119)
- Labor Chronicle (Reel 1) (Reel 120)
- Labor News (Reel 1) (Reel 121)
- Labor News (Reel 3) (Reel 122)
- Labor News (Reel 4) (Reel 123)
- Labor News Rochester (Reel 1) (Reel 124)
- Labor Notes (Reel 1) (Reel 125)
- The Lampmaker (Reel 1) (Reel 126)
- The Lampmaker (Reel 2) (Reel 127)
- The Liberator (Reel 1) (Reel 128)
- Local 6 News (Reel 1) (Reel 129)
- Local 1199 Hospital News (Reel 1) (Reel 130)
- Longshore News (Reel 1) (Reel 131)
- Maintenance of Way Guide (Reel 1) (Reel 132)
- Mechanic (Reel 1) (Reel 133)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 1) (Reel 134)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 1) (Reel 135)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 2) (Reel 136)
- The Messenger (Reel 1) (Reel 137)
- The Messenger (Reel 2) (Reel 138)
- Michigan Labor Leader (Reel 1) (Reel 139)
- National Labour Journal (Reel 1) (Reel 140)
- National Laborer (Reel 1) (Reel 141)
- The Negro Worker (Reel 1) (Reel 142)
- New Leader (Reel 1) (Reel 143)
- Mechanics Free Press (Reel 1) (Reel 144)
- The N.Y. Longshoremen (Reel 1) (Reel 145)
- ILR Announcements (Reel 1) (Reel 146)
- New York Teacher (Reel 1) (Reel 147)
- New York Teacher (Reel 2) (Reel 148)
- New York Teacher (Reel 3) (Reel 149)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 3) (Reel 150)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 4) (Reel 151)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 5) (Reel 152)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 6) (Reel 153)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 7) (Reel 154)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 8) (Reel 155)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 9) (Reel 156)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 10) (Reel 157)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 11) (Reel 158)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 12) (Reel 159)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 13) (Reel 160)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 14) (Reel 161)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 15) (Reel 162)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 16) (Reel 163)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 17) (Reel 164)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 18) (Reel 165)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 19) (Reel 166)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 20) (Reel 167)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 21) (Reel 168)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 22) (Reel 169)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 23) (Reel 170)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 24) (Reel 171)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 25) (Reel 172)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 26) (Reel 173)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 27) (Reel 174)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 28) (Reel 175)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 29) (Reel 176)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 30) (Reel 177)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 31) (Reel 178)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 32) (Reel 179)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 33) (Reel 180)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 34) (Reel 181)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 35) (Reel 182)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 36) (Reel 183)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 37) (Reel 184)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 38) (Reel 185)
- New York Volkeitzung (Reel 39) (Reel 186)
- Packinghouse Worker (Reel 1) (Reel 187)
- Penn AFL-CIO News (Reel 1) (Reel 188)
- People (Reel 1) (Reel 189)
- Pittsburgh Socialist (Reel 1) (Reel 190)
- Pittsburgh Socialist (Reel 2) (Reel 191)
- Public Employee Address (Reel 1) (Reel 192)
- Pulp and Paper Worker (Reel 1) (Reel 193)
- Railroad Brakeman's Journal (Reel 1) (Reel 194)
- Railroad Telegrapher (Reel 1) (Reel 195)
- Railroad Telegrapher (Reel 2) (Reel 196)
- Railroad Telegrapher (Reel 3) (Reel 197)
- Railroad Telegrapher (Reel 4) (Reel 198)
- Railroad Telegrapher (Reel 5) (Reel 199)
- Railroad Telegrapher (Reel 6) (Reel 200)
- Railroad Telegrapher (Reel 7) (Reel 201)
- Cataloged (Reel 1) (Reel 202)
- Republik Der Arbeiter (Reel 1) (Reel 203)
- Department Store Employee (Reel 1) (Reel 204)
- Department Store Employee (Reel 2) (Reel 205)
- Steel Labor (Reel 1) (Reel 206)
- Rochester Vicinity Labor Herald (Reel 1) (Reel 207)
- Stranded Oiler (Reel 1) (Reel 208)
- Survey (Reel 1) (Reel 209)
- Survey (Reel 2) (Reel 210)
- Switchman's Journal (Reel 1) (Reel 211)
- Switchman's Journal (Reel 2) (Reel 212)
- Switchman's Journal (Reel 3) (Reel 213)
- Taylor Society (Reel 1) (Reel 214)
- Timber Worker (Reel 1) (Reel 215)
- Timber Worker (Reel 2) (Reel 216)
- Trade Union Leagues (Reel 1) (Reel 217)
- U E News (Reel 1) (Reel 218)
- U.S.S. Steel News (Reel 1) (Reel 219)
- U.S.S. Steel News (Reel 2) (Reel 220)
- U.S.S. Steel News (Reel 3) (Reel 221)
- The Union Leader (Reel 1) (Reel 222)
- The Union Leader (Reel 2) (Reel 223)
- Union Teacher (Reel 1) (Reel 224)
- Union Voice (Reel 1) (Reel 225)
- Union Voice (Reel 2) (Reel 226)
- Union Voice (Reel 3) (Reel 227)
- United Automobile Worker (Reel 1) (Reel 228)
- United Automobile Worker (Reel 2) (Reel 229)
- United Rubber Worker (Reel 1) (Reel 230)
- United Mine Workers Journal (Reel 1) (Reel 231)
- United Mine Workers Journal (Reel 2) (Reel 232)
- United Teacher (Reel 2) (Reel 233)
- United Teacher (Reel 3) (Reel 234)
- United Teacher (Reel 4) (Reel 235)
- United Teacher (Reel 5) (Reel 236)
- United Teacher (Reel 6) (Reel 237)
- The Voice of 770 (Reel 1) (Reel 238)
- The Voice of 770 (Reel 2) (Reel 239)
- Welt Der Arbeit (Reel 1) (Reel 240)
- The People (Reel 1) (Reel 241)
- The People (Reel 2) (Reel 242)
- The People (Reel 3) (Reel 243)
- Weekly People (Reel 1) (Reel 244)
- Weekly People (Reel 2) (Reel 245)
- Weekly People (Reel 3) (Reel 246)
- Weekly People (Reel 4) (Reel 247)
- Weekly People (Reel 5) (Reel 248)
- Weekly People (Reel 6) (Reel 249)
- Weekly People (Reel 7) (Reel 250)
- The Workingman's Advocate (Reel 1) (Reel 251)
- The Workingman's Advocate (Reel 2) (Reel 252)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 1) (Reel 253)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 2) (Reel 254)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 3) (Reel 255)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 4) (Reel 256)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 5) (Reel 257)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 6) (Reel 258)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 7) (Reel 259)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 8) (Reel 260)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 9) (Reel 261)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 10) (Reel 262)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 11) (Reel 263)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 12) (Reel 264)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 13) (Reel 265)
- The Working Press (Reel 1) (Reel 266)
- The Working Press (Reel 2) (Reel 267)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 14) (Reel 268)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 15) (Reel 269)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 16) (Reel 270)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 17) (Reel 271)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 18) (Reel 272)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 19) (Reel 273)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 20) (Reel 274)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 21) (Reel 275)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 22) (Reel 276)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 23) (Reel 277)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 24) (Reel 278)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 25) (Reel 279)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 26) (Reel 280)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 27) (Reel 281)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 28) (Reel 282)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 29) (Reel 283)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 30) (Reel 284)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 31) (Reel 285)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 32) (Reel 286)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 33) (Reel 287)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 34) (Reel 288)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 35) (Reel 289)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 36) (Reel 290)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 37) (Reel 291)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 38) (Reel 292)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 39) (Reel 293)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 40) (Reel 294)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 41) (Reel 295)
- Labor-News Rochester (Reel 42) (Reel 296)
- The Carpenter (Reel 1) (Reel 297)
- The Carpenter (Reel 2) (Reel 298)
- The Carpenter (Reel 3) (Reel 299)
- The Carpenter (Reel 4) (Reel 300)
- The Carpenter (Reel 5) (Reel 301)
- The Carpenter (Reel 6) (Reel 302)
- The Carpenter (Reel 7) (Reel 303)
- The Carpenter (Reel 8) (Reel 304)
- The Carpenter (Reel 9) (Reel 305)
- The Carpenter (Reel 10) (Reel 306)
- The Carpenter (Reel 11) (Reel 307)
- The Carpenter (Reel 12) (Reel 308)
- The Carpenter (Reel 13) (Reel 309)
- The Carpenter (Reel 14) (Reel 310)
- The Carpenter (Reel 15) (Reel 311)
- The Carpenter (Reel 16) (Reel 312)
- The Carpenter (Reel 17) (Reel 313)
- The Carpenter (Reel 18) (Reel 314)
- The Carpenter (Reel 19) (Reel 315)
- The Carpenter (Reel 20) (Reel 316)
- The Carpenter (Reel 21) (Reel 317)
- The Carpenter (Reel 22) (Reel 318)
- The Carpenter (Reel 23) (Reel 319)
- The Carpenter (Reel 24) (Reel 320)
- The Carpenter (Reel 25) (Reel 321)
- The Carpenter (Reel 26) (Reel 322)
- The Carpenter (Reel 27) (Reel 323)
- The Carpenter (Reel 28) (Reel 324)
- The Carpenter (Reel 29) (Reel 325)
- The Carpenter (Reel 30) (Reel 326)
- The Carpenter (Reel 31) (Reel 327)
- The Carpenter (Reel 32) (Reel 328)
- The Carpenter (Reel 33) (Reel 329)
- The Carpenter (Reel 34) (Reel 330)
- Buffalo Union Leader (Reel 1) (Reel 331)
- Buffalo Union Leader (Reel 2) (Reel 332)
- Union Leader (Reel 1) (Reel 333)
- Union Leader (Reel 2) (Reel 334)
- Union Leader (Reel 3) (Reel 335)
- Union Leader (Reel 4) (Reel 336)
- Union Leader (Reel 5) (Reel 337)
- Union Leader (Reel 6) (Reel 338)
- Union Leader (Reel 7) (Reel 339)
- Mulcaire, Michael Aloysius (Reel 1) (Reel 340)
- Mulcaire, Michael Aloysius (Reel 2) (Reel 341)
- Cataloged Microfilm No.99 (Reel 99) (Reel 342)
- "History of the Papermakers" (Reel 1) (Reel 343)
- The Chinese Labor Movement (Reel 1) (Reel 344)
- Society of Mechanics and Tradesmen N.Y. (Reel 1) (Reel 345)
- Chicago Anarchists 1886 (Reel 1) (Reel 346)
- Thomas Hunter b.1796 Trial (Reel 1) (Reel 347)
- Trial of the Journeyman Cordwainers (Reel 1) (Reel 348)
- International Labor Office (Reel 1) (Reel 349)
- Josef Lens (Reel 1) (Reel 350)
- Jules Louis Breton (Reel 1) (Reel 351)
- Jules Guesde (Reel 1) (Reel 352)
- Heinrich Rau (Reel 1) (Reel 353)
- Jean Longuet (Reel 1) (Reel 354)
- Syndacalisme et Socialisme (Reel 1) (Reel 355)
- Union of Distillery Workers (Reel 1) (Reel 356)
- Solomon Abramovich Dridzo (Reel 1) (Reel 357)
- Journeymen Painters (Reel 1) (Reel 358)
- Int'l Trade Union Movement (Reel 1) (Reel 359)
- Int'l Trade Union Movement (Reel 2) (Reel 360)
- Int'l of Labor Unions (Reel 1) (Reel 361)
- John Warren Beckwith (Reel 1) (Reel 362)
- Walter Michael Lacyk (Reel 1) (Reel 363)
- Bricklayers (Reel 1) (Reel 364)
- United Assn. of Journeymen Plumbers (Reel 1) (Reel 365)
- United. Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners (Reel 1) (Reel 366)
- United. Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners (Reel 2) (Reel 367)
- United. Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners (Reel 3) (Reel 368)
- United. Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners (Reel 4) (Reel 369)
- United. Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners (Reel 5) (Reel 370)
- Cigar Makers Union (Reel 1) (Reel 371)
- Impact of Russian Rev. on AFL (Reel 1) (Reel 372)
- International Brotherhood of Papermakers (Reel 1) (Reel 373)
- Korean Labor Movement (Reel 1) (Reel 374)
- Iron, Steel, Tin workers Association (Reel 1) (Reel 375)
- Iron, Steel, Tin workers Association (Reel 2) (Reel 376)
- Bernhard Becker (Reel 1) (Reel 377)
- The American Laborer (Reel 1) (Reel 378)
- Donald Frederick Welland (Reel 1) (Reel 379)
- Daniel de Leon (Reel 1) (Reel 380)
- Daniel de Leon (Reel 2) (Reel 381)
- National Union of Marine Cooks and Stewards (Reel 1) (Reel 382)
- Thomas Jefferson Kerr IV (Reel 1) (Reel 383)
- Eliot J. Berg (Reel 1) (Reel 384)
- Richard S. Crutchfield (Reel 1) (Reel 385)
- Stanley E. Barnes (Reel 1) (Reel 386)
- Jack Charles Robert Camm (Reel 1) (Reel 387)
- Alan Christopher Davies (Reel 1) (Reel 388)
- R.B. Davison (Reel 1) (Reel 389)
- International Union of Mine, Mill, Smelter Workers (Reel 1) (Reel 390)
- International Union of Mine, Mill, Smelter Workers (Reel 2) (Reel 391)
- Thomas Firmin (Reel 1) (Reel 392)
- British Parlimt. Child Labor 1816 (Reel 1) (Reel 393)
- Herbert Buchner (Reel 1) (Reel 394)
- Joseph Hanson 1809 (Reel 1) (Reel 395)
- Eleonore Hacker 1963 (Reel 1) (Reel 396)
- Avril Ernest Harris (Reel 1) (Reel 397)
- Mary Howitt (Reel 1) (Reel 398)
- Wolfgang Hacker (Reel 1) (Reel 399)
- Edward Kellogg (Reel 1) (Reel 400)
- Hans Georg Jungblut (Reel 1) (Reel 401)
- Harriet Martineau (Reel 1) (Reel 402)
- Miriam Horris (Reel 1) (Reel 403)
- Daniel Patrick Moynihan (Reel 1) (Reel 404)
- Karl Heinz Mucher (Reel 1) (Reel 405)
- Rita Munster (Reel 1) (Reel 406)
- Heinrich Nilges (Reel 1) (Reel 407)
- Stanley Rosen (Reel 1) (Reel 408)
- Heinz Rosenbauer (Reel 1) (Reel 409)
- The Socialist alliance (Reel 1) (Reel 410)
- United Labor Party (Reel 1) (Reel 411)
- William Thomas Thornton (Reel 1) (Reel 412)
- 1827 Trial Tailors Conspiracy (Reel 1) (Reel 413)
- Armin Volze (Reel 1) (Reel 414)
- Hans Dieter Vaasan (Reel 1) (Reel 415)
- Erwin Wiesmuller (Reel 1) (Reel 416)
- United Mine Workers of America (Reel 1) (Reel 417)
- United Mine Workers of America (Reel 2) (Reel 418)
- Entrepeneurial History (Reel 1) (Reel 419)
- Jahrbuch fur Frauenarbeit (Reel 1) (Reel 420)
- Bureau of National Affairs Washington (Reel 1) (Reel 421)
- Bureau of National Affairs Washington (Reel 2) (Reel 422)
- La participation de l'entrepreneur (Reel 1) (Reel 423)
- National Women's Trade Union (Reel 1) (Reel 424)
- Ladies' Society Locomotive Firemen (Reel 1) (Reel 425)
- International Federation of Building and Woodworkers (Reel 1) (Reel 426)
- Malcriado (English Version) (Reel 1) (Reel 427)
- New York Teacher News (Reel 1) (Reel 428)
- New York Teacher News (Reel 2) (Reel 429)
- New York Teacher News (Reel 3) (Reel 430)
- New York Teacher News (Reel 4) (Reel 431)
- Jeffrey Newman (Reel 1) (Reel 432)
- FLM Joint Board Tempo (Reel 1) (Reel 433)
- Freedom Socialist Party U.S.A (Reel 1) (Reel 434)
- B&W Boilermaker (Reel 1) (Reel 435)
- Ithaca Union Labor Review (Reel 1) (Reel 436)
- Union Labor Advocate (Reel 1) (Reel 437)
- Union Labor Advocate (Reel 2) (Reel 438)
- UE News (Reel 1) (Reel 439)
- Labor (Reel 1) (Reel 440)
- Labor (Reel 2) (Reel 441)
- The Washington Teamster (Reel 1) (Reel 442)
- The Brookwood Review (Reel 1) (Reel 443)
- The Trade Unionist (Reel 1) (Reel 444)
- Tamiment Institute (Reel 1) (Reel 445)
- Herald 1931-1933 (Reel 1) (Reel 446)
- Herald 1933-1936 (Reel 2) (Reel 447)
- Herald 1936-1939 (Reel 3) (Reel 448)
- Herald 1939-1940 (Reel 4) (Reel 449)
- Herald 1940-1942 (Reel 5) (Reel 450)
- The Chief (Reel 1) (Reel 451)
- The Chief (Reel 2) (Reel 452)
- The Chief (Reel 3) (Reel 453)
- The Chief (Reel 4) (Reel 454)
- The Chief (Reel 5) (Reel 455)
- The Chief (Reel 6) (Reel 456)
- The Chief (Reel 7) (Reel 457)
- The Chief (Reel 8) (Reel 458)
- The Chief (Reel 9) (Reel 459)
- The Chief (Reel 10) (Reel 460)
- The Chief (Reel 11) (Reel 461)
- The Chief (Reel 12) (Reel 462)
- The Chief (Reel 13) (Reel 463)
- The Chief (Reel 14) (Reel 464)
- The Chief (Reel 15) (Reel 465)
- The Chief (Reel 16) (Reel 466)
- The Chief (Reel 17) (Reel 467)
- The Chief (Reel 18) (Reel 468)
- The Chief (Reel 19) (Reel 469)
- The Chief (Reel 20) (Reel 470)
- The Chief (Reel 21) (Reel 471)
- The Chief (Reel 22) (Reel 472)
- The Chief (Reel 23) (Reel 473)
- The Chief (Reel 24) (Reel 474)
- The Chief (Reel 25) (Reel 475)
- Central Labor Council (Reel 1) (Reel 476)
- Central Labor Council (Reel 2) (Reel 477)
- Shingle Weaver (Reel 1) (Reel 478)
- Shingle Weaver (Reel 2) (Reel 479)
- Shingle Weaver (Reel 3) (Reel 480)
- Shingle Weaver (Reel 4) (Reel 481)
- The Labor Management News (Reel 1) (Reel 482)
- The Labor Management News (Reel 2) (Reel 483)
- Glassworker (Reel 1) (Reel 484)
- Voice of the Marine Cooks (Reel 1) (Reel 485)
- The National Trades' Union (Reel 1) (Reel 486)